Contact

nancy.richardson79@gmail.co

www.linkedin.com/in/imani-chirarichardson-01b004a5 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel ACLS

Languages

Italian Swahili

Imani Chira-Richardson

BSN-Board Certified, CCRN

Richmond, Virginia

Summary

Bachelor's prepared Registered Nurse, Compact licensed in(Virginia Multi-state privilege), NY, NJ, MN, CT, Oregon. Pending (CA, MA, PA, WA) with 8+years of experience in critical care with a passion and drive for quality patient safety, care and use of evidence based research for best patient outcomes. Multi-specialties trained and experienced in different adult ICU settings. Experienced travel nurse at hospitals ranging from level 1 trauma to community hospitals, working rapid responses, Emar conversions, disaster and very well versed in the use of Epic, Cerner and Meditech.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions RN, CCRN June 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month) Northside Hospital, Tampa, FL

Hurricane Irma disaster relief work for 30 days and per diem for their HCA hospitals ICU needs.

UVA Health System RN, CCRN - travel assignment Neuro ICU September 2017 - April 2018 (8 months) Charlottsville, VA

Inova Health System
CCRN, Trauma ICU nurse
June 2017 - September 2017 (4 months)
Trauma ICU-Level 1 trauma hospital

Travel assignment TRAUMA ICU

Yale New Haven Hospital
BSN, RN, CCRN - Medical ICU
January 2017 - June 2017 (6 months)
New Haven, Connecticut

56 bed medical ICU at Yale New Haven, travel assignment.

Bon Secours Health System
BSN, RN, PCCN
January 2014 - March 2017 (3 years 3 months)

Inova Health System RN, CCRN, CVICU/cardiac surgery June 2016 - December 2016 (7 months) Fairfax, Virginia

From trauma ICU to cardiac surgery ICU nursing.

CJW Medical Center BSN, RN, TNCC - trauma medical ICU October 2014 - June 2016 (1 year 9 months)

VCU Health System
Care Partner
January 2012 - January 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Education

SOUTH UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2013)

University of Nairobi
Bachelor of Science - BS, Chemistry · (2002)